why are your guys
из-за чего Ваши ребята
dying Well, for the sake of peace I don't know
умирают Ну за то чтобы был я не знаю мир
I think it's good And who is the emperor of the
Я думаю хорошо А кто сейчас император
Austro-Hungarian
австро-венгерской
Empire now I also don't
империи тоже не
know
знаю
Hello, hello Hello, you are
Привет здравствуйте Здравствуйте вы
cute
симпатично
Thank you very much I'm looking for a
Очень спасибо большое я я я шукаю
boy don't look I'm from Ukraine but I
хлопчика не смотрите Я из Украины но я
I quarrel with people from Russia I understand that
ссорюсь с людьми из России Я понимаю что
you are not guilty That's because you are not
вы не виноваты Вот потому что вы не
responsible for the actions of
несёте ответственность за действие
your government this has
своего правительства это ещё с Древнего
been the principle since ancient Rome that a slave is not
Рима есть принцип что раб не несёт
responsible for his master
ответственности за своего хозяина
That's why I have no complaints against you
Поэтому я у меня к вам нет Никаких
Let's do the same to you  My
претензий а давайте как вас зовут Меня
name is Lera Lera Can I still talk to your
зовут Лера Лера Можно я ещё с вашей
friend Well, by Hello
подружкой пообщаюсь Ну по Приветствую
because since she is a friend What is her name
потому что раз она подружка Как её зовут
at all not with me my friend since Well,
вобще не со мной своим другом раз Ну
let me not just by Hello
дайте не я просто по Приветствую потому
because it is uncultured for me if I talk to a
что у меня некультурно если я общаюсь с
girl I didn't greet her with  her
девушкой не поприветствовал с её
friend She just doesn't really want to be
подругой Она просто не особо хочет в
seen in the camera she can say so
камере светиться она может так м сказать
once No just once show her the
один раз Нет один раз просто покажите ей
eyes and we'll continue to communicate with
поприветствуем глаза и будем дальше с
you
вами
Well she doesn't want I don't want  I can't
общаться Ну она не хочет не хочет я не
force a person no If you
могу заставить человека нет Если вы
want us to communicate I have to say
хотите чтобы мы общались я должен
hello to your girlfriend otherwise
поздороваться С вашей подружкой иначе
No well okay then Yes I won't
Нет ну хорошо тогда Да я не буду
look for you boy that's it then
вас хлопчика искать вот здесь всё тогда
goodbye you have a cute kitty I
до свидания у вас милый котик
got it And who do you think
вот понял А ты как считаешь чей
Crimea is honestly I don't  I want to get into this
Крым честно я не хочу в это вникать
because I don't know And I don't understand
потому что не знаю И я не разбираюсь в
politics so I won't leave this topic
политике поэтому я не будуть с этой темы
And how old are you 18 I understand What do you
А сколько тебе лет 18 понял Кем
do for a living I don't work I study What are you studying to be a
работаешь Я не работаю я учусь
pastry chef I
учишься на повара кондитера
understand And who do you think is to blame for
понял А как ты считаешь кто виноват в
the fact that  Russia attacked
том что Россия напала на
Ukraine honestly they are both guilty I think
Украину честно виноваты Я думаю оба
because people who should
Потому что люди которые должны
be presidents should be
находиться в президентах должны быть
smart well I don't mean to insult I
умными ну я как бы не оскорбляю я имею в
mean people who Well they should be
виду люди которые Ну должны находиться в
presidents they should
президентах они должны вот как бы
understand that war is not very good
понимать что война - это не очень хорошо
And as if harm to all, not only to
Да и как бы вред всем не только
specific countries that are fighting among
конкретным странам которые воюют между
themselves, and a person who should
собой и человек как бы который должен
be presidents. This should be
находиться президентах Это должен
understood, and so if all this
понимать а значит если вот это всё
started, then they have everything under control and they
началось Значит у них всё схвачено и они
either already know the outcome of events and know what
либо уже знают исход событий и знают что
they will suffer there.  something something they know that
они потерпят там что-то что-то знают что
everything is like this now that's all that is I
вот так всё как сейчас вот всё то есть я
understood correctly that you called Putin a
правильно понял что вы назвали Путина
fool
глупцом
I called everyone
я назвала всех
a fool Well and Putin too it
глупцом Ну и Путина в том числе
turns out that Putin is a
получается что Путин
little fool Well how little he attacked another
слегка Ну как слегка он напал на другую
country then he  a complete idiot they kill
страну то он полностью глупец убивают
his people by the way do you know
его людей у Вас кстати из знакомых есть
anyone who died in
кто-то кто погиб на
the war no not yet but they are fighting and fighting and there are
войне Нет нету ещё но воюют воюют А
wounded there without a leg arm
раненые есть там без ноги руки
no no I understand
бе Нет нету понял
and what do you think guys
а как вы считаете за что умирают ребята
from
из
Russia are dying for oh I'm saying I  I don't understand
России ой я вот говорю я не понимаю я
anything about politics Well, I mean, because of what
ничего в политике Ну в смысле из-за че
again Well, because of what are your guys
как ещё раз Ну из-за чего Ваши ребята
dying Well, so that there would be, I don't know, peace
умирают Ну за то чтобы был я не знаю мир
I think that is, they started the war so that there would
Я думаю то есть они начали войну чтобы
be peace
был мир
Well, well, well, and so that they would win  yeah
Да ну ну и чтобы они победили да
Wait they started a war so they could
Подожди они начали войну чтобы они
win yeah I think it's like well they started a
победили Да думаю это как ну начали
war in order to win why
войну для того чтобы победить А зачем
win but to prove that
побеждать а для того чтобы доказать что
they are alpha males and they will bend the whole world
они альфа-самцы и они на гнут весь мир
yeah And what do you think is it right
будет Угу А как ты считаешь Правильно ли
that the Russians attacked  another country
что россияне напали на другую страну
to prove  that they are alpha males and they will
чтобы доказать что они альфа-самцы и они
bend the whole world once again.
на гнут весь мир ищё раз
What do you think? Did
Как ты считаешь Правильно ли сделали
the Russians do the right thing by attacking another country
россияне что напали на другую страну
in order to prove that they are
ради того чтобы доказать что они
alpha males?
альфа-самцы
Well, I think there was a reason for this and at
Ну я думаю этому была причина и как
least the words of the president, it turns out, are
минимум слова президента получается
yours. I think that  a person who
вашего Я думаю что человек который
is in the presidency he should not
находится в президентах он не должен
somehow with his other spheres and somehow
как-то своими другими сферами и каким-то
I don’t even know how to
я даже не знаю как это
explain it I don’t know everything you
объяснить я как бы всего не знаю
understand You better ask me
понимаете Вы меня луше спрашивайте
because And what
потому что А какие какие какие слова
were the words of our president I something  I don't
были нашего президента Я что-то не
quite
совсем
understand I don't know I don't remember specific words
понял Не знаю я не помню конкретных слов
I only remember the behavior he
я помню лишь поведение которое он
showed when he was president and before
показывал когда был и до президентом и
and after and
после и во
during So how should this behavior of a
время Вот и как бы это поведение совсем
president be I think I
президента должно быть я считаю вот мне
understand I'm interested yes and what what what are you
понял мне интересно да а что что что вы
remember his behavior before and after the president
помните с его поведения до президента и
Well, at least I remember that Putin tried to
Ну как минимум Я помню что Путин пытался
come to a peaceful solution, but Zelensky did
прийти к мирному решению но Зеленский
n’t seem to react or
вроде как не отреагировал либо
reacted somehow rudely or something I
отреагировал как-то грубовато или что я
don’t remember You
не помню Понимаете
see, if I’m not mistaken If you are 18 years old
вот если я не ошибаюсь Если вам 18 лет
when Zelensky was still  you weren't president
когда Зеленский ещё не был президентом
you were
вам было
13 Well  it turns out that what do you remember about
13 Ну получается чтом что вы помните о
NM from this
НМ из этого
period He seemed to participate in KVN
периода Он вроде как в КВНе участвовал
or something like that, so is that bad or what? It's not
или что-то подобном так это плохо что
bad,
ли Это неплохо
but he just manages to contribute to this
но просто он эту
sphere
сферу как бы
and his presidential post or
и свой вот этот вот президентский пост
something I don't even understand  how to
что ли Я даже не понимаю как это
explain it In
объяснить В
general, here's
общем вот
what Putin worked for us, that the suitcase is
наме Путин работал тем что чемодан
for the mayor of St. Petersburg Well, and
за мэром санкт-петербурга Да ну и он
now he's trying to do this in his Presidential
теперь это пробует в своё Президентское
Here's what's the
Вот это всё вносить какая
difference
разница
Yes, to be honest, I don't know, I understood, that's
Да если честно не знаю понял я вот
why I don't want to talk about this topic I
поэтому я не хочу говорить на эту тему я
what's good question question And how does it
что хорошо вопрос вопрос А как так
happen yes What
получается да Что
uh all NATO countries support
ээ все страны НАТО вот поддерживают
Ukraine and
Украину и
uh from France Yes Napoleon also
ээ из Франции Да вот Наполеон тоже
supported
поддержал
Zelensky I don't even know how to react to this
Зеленского не знаю даже как на это
to be
реагировать если
honest Well this Prime Minister of
честно Ну вот этот премьер-министр
France Napoleon Bonaparte Yes he said
Франции Наполеон Бонапарт Да он сказал
that France  will supply Ukraine with guns, how do
что Франция поставит Украине пушки как
you feel about this?
ты к этому
Well, let them supply them, I don't even know
относишься Ну пусть ставят не знаю даже
what to
что
say. Well, okay, and the Swedish
говорить Ну а хорошо а шведский
example also says that they, for example,
пример тоже говорит что они например в
will send military aid to Poltava,
Полтаву отправят ээ помощь военную
Ukraine, how do you feel about this?
Украине как ты к этому
No way, honestly,
никак честно
no way. Well, how? Well, okay.  eh
никак лити Ну как Ну хорошо ээ О'кей
Okay okay
ладно
and to the fact that for example England yes England
а к тому что например Англия да Англия
Great Britain is sending its
Великобритания направляет свои
royal regiments regiments to
королевские полка полки в
Ukraine How do you feel about this
Украину Как ты относишься к этому
in any way you understand I don't understand this
никак вы понимаете Я не разбираюсь в это
topic In general I think that it is
теме В общем я думаю что это мне
not me who should leave I am fine You are the first first
уходить не я нормально Вы первый первая
girl  who communicates normally in the
девушка которая нормально общается в
forehead I am interested as a common person
челе Мне интересно как простой человек с
to talk to you as a common person and how do
вами простым человеком поговорить да как
you understand this A ok
вы это понимаете А хорошо
question who is now Yes who is
вопрос кто сейчас Да кто
now Queen of the United States of
сейчас Королева Соединённых Штатов
America I also know you
Америки тоже знаю
understand sleepy States of
понимаете сонных Штатов
America
Америки
you
ю
understood Yeah ok And who is now the emperor of the
понял Угу хорошо А кто сейчас император
Austro-Hungarian
австро-венгерской
Empire  I don't know either You're all singing all
империи тоже не знаю Всё вот поете все
the questions concerning some history Yes,
вопросы касающиеся истории какой-либо Да
they will be destroyed and you won't get any answers You don't have to
они они будут уничтожены и ответов вы не
ask me about A
получите можете меня не спрашивать по А
OK And why did Lenin create Ukraine
хорошо А почему Ленин создал Украину
Lenin created Ukraine What's new I
Ленин создал Украину Что за новенькое
wanted apparently why are there so few
по захотелось видимо почему так мало
cities from OK  AK Who is Stepan
городов из хорошо АК Кто такой Степан
Bandera, you know Stepan
Бандера вы знаете Степан
Bandera, something is familiar, but I don’t know, it
Бандера знакомое что-то но я не знаю
turns out, Yeah, and Ukrainians and Russians are
получается Угу а украинцы и русские -
one
это один
people, I think, yes, we are all people, we all
народ думаю да ведь мы все люди мы все
come from the same family  Yes, yes, we are all
произошли из одного рода Да да мы все
people, I understand. And for example, Americans and
люди понял А например Американцы и
Russians are one people. Well, I think so, because
русский один народ Ну я считаю да потому
we all came from the same world, from the
что ну мы все появились одного света с
same place. Oh, excuse my French.
одного Ой извиняюсь за мой французский
We are all, as it were, one whole. Roughly
Мы все как бы одно целое грубо
speaking, it’s just that some people have their own language,
говоря просто у кого-то свой язык свои
their own traditions.  principle and so on And
традиции свои принцип и так далее А как
how Whose Crimea do you think?
Как вы считаете чей
No idea Crimea doesn't
Крым Без понятия Крым ничему никому не
belong to anyone, it just exists and that's
принадлежит он просто существует и всё
it Well, what kind of country is Crimea, I
на этом Ну Крым это какая
mean, what kind of country should I
страна в смысле какая как я долже на
answer this question Well, Crimea What
этот вопрос ответить Ну Крым В какой
country
стране
is it in
находится в
Ukraine, I guess  I don't I'm
Украине наверное я Я не Я вот
saying I got a 3 in geography I don't even
говорю я у меня по географии 3 я даже не
know where anything is Well no Why do I know
знаю где что находится Ну нет Зачем знаю
but not in such minute details
но но не в таких мельчайших подробностях
roughly speaking I'm saying I don't touch on
грубо говоря я говорю я не касаюсь
politics and I don't touch on this whole problem of
политики и не касаюсь всей этой проблемы
this whole war I'm not interested in it
всей этой войны меня она не интересует
Well, how are you not interested but for
Ну как ты тебя не интересует но
some reason I know about Zelensky Everything about him
почему-то знае о зеленском Всё что он
before the war, what he was like during the war I
был до войны что он во время войны не
can’t understand because he was a comedian and
могу понять потому что он был комиком и
I watched him and that’s all I remember is
я его смотрела и всё вот я помню только
this and I remember his words his actions  I
вот это и помню его слова его действия
understand everything. And what did he not want there?
всё понима А что он там не захотел мир
Some kind of peace, you say? Well, yes, because
какой-то вы говорите Ну да потому что
Vladimir  Vladimirovich Putin, he proposed
Владимир Владимирович Путин он предлагал
peace, he proposed to solve
мир он предлагал решить
everything, I don’t know, T apparently disappeared, I had no
всё я не знаю Т слился видать я без
idea, I didn’t watch, I only remember that there
понятия не смотрела Я помню лишь то что
seemed to be no answer, I didn’t watch
ответа вроде как не было я не смотрела
the negotiations, I’m saying I can’t vouch for this topic,
переговоры Я говорю я в этой теме не
so I think if Well, there
ручаюсь поэтому я думаю если Ну вопросов
won’t be any questions  except this topic I think I
не будет кроме этой темы Я думаю мне
should leave it won't be good
стоит уходить не будет будет хорошо
let's except this topic yes And for example and
давайте кроме этой темы да А например а
not on history And now Who heads the
не по истории А сейчас Кто возглавляет
State Duma of the Russian
Государственную Думу Российской
Federation
Федерации
you know
знаете
no syu is not a mandatory factor in order
нет сю не обязательный фактор для того
not to exist in this world Okay
чтобы не существовать в этом мире О'кей
and cities  Russian Federation you
а города Российской Федерации вы
know I think that I will not be able to answer
знаете думаю что я не смогу ответить на
this question because you yourself From what
этот вопрос пото вы сами Из какого
city what you yourself From what
города что вы сами Из какого
city from Chelny and Naberezhnye Chelny
города с Челнов а Набережные Челны
Tatarstan Yes my father is from Kazan
Татарстан Да у меня отец из Казани родом
Yeah let's be interesting here I want to
Угу давайте интересно вот я хочу
check let me name two
проверить давайте я буду называть два
cities one in Russia the other not in Russia
города один в России другой не в России
you will try to guess which one is in
вы будете пробовать угадать какой в
Russia Yeah, let's let's let's
России Угу давайте давайте давайте
start with the simple St. Petersburg and
начнём с простого санкт-петербург и
Paris Well, obviously Paris is not in Russia but I
Париж Ну явно Париж не в России а са так
understand okay let's e Birabidzhan and
понял хорошо давайте э Бирабиджан и
Tuapse
Туапсе
Well  Birobidzhan probably not but in general yes
Ну Биробиджан наверное нет а вообще да
right So good let's do it like
правильно Так хорошо давайте ээ сделаем
this they gave and
так дали и
Islamabad again
исламабад ещё раз
Delhi is the first city and the second
Дели первый город а второй
Islamabad Probably Islamabad is in
исламабад Наверное исламабад - это в
Russia And the first no right right
России А первые нет правильно правильно
super Well now such Kabul and
супер Хорошо теперь такой э Кабул и
Tehran is the
Тегеран
second in Russia and the first no right
второй в России а Первый нет правильно
Okay now Cairo and
Хорошо теперь Каир и
Ankara Cairo probably not and the second one in
Анкара Каир наверное нет а второй в
Russia was wrong wrong the other way around Cairo in
России ошиблись ошиблись наоборот Каир в
Russia is so good Vienna and
России так хорошо Вена и
Budapest Budapest Damn well that's another
Будапешт Будапешт Блин ну это другая
country But it's like
страна Но это вроде
Russia rules correctly well done yeah Okay
Россия прави правильно молодец да Хорошо
now Bucharest and Sofia
теперь Бухарест и София
probably Sofia
наверное София
Russian I mean you understood that  here is the
русский В смысле это вы поняли вот
second one correctly Vilnius and
второй правильно Вильнюс и
Riga Riga is no definitely not And in Russia
Рига Рига это нет точно нет А в России
Vilnius got it right Helsinki and
Вильнюс правильно понял Хельсинки и
Tallinn Helsinki is definitely not correct yes
Таллин Хельсинки точно нет правильно да
And Tallinn in Russia is super well done Good
А талин в России супер молодец Хорошо
Berlin and
Берлин и
Bonn
Бон
Well Berlin is definitely not logical Berlin is
Ну Берлин точно нет логично Берлин
Germany and Bonn is Russia correct
Германия а Бон - это России правильно
So Paris  and
Так Париж и
Madrid probably Madrid Well it's unlikely but for
Мадрид наверное Мадрид Ну это вряд ли но
some reason I doubt that no oh what yes
почему-то я сомневаюсь что нет ой что да
what is he in Russia wait then who is in Russia who is
что он в Рос подожди то кто в России кто
not in Russia here is a bet and
не в России вот пари и
Madrid is not here  there is no catch there
Мадрид здесь нет подвоха Потому что нету
is no catch that means Paris is
нету подвоха нету подвоха значит Париж
not Russia right Paris is France
не Россия правильно Париж - Это Франция
because that is where my Phillips Tower is that
потому что там моя филея башня это
was a simple question yes Madrid is in Russia yes
простой вопрос был да Мадрид в России да
it is in Adygea it is located yes okay that is the
это в Адыгее находится он да хорошо
question Let's take now uh so
вопрос такой Давай сейчас возьмём э так
uh
ээ
Vancouver and
Ванкувер и
Chicago  Chicago No definitely not in Russia but the
Чикаго Чикаго Нет точно не в России а
first in Russia Okay Prague and
первый в России О'кей Прага и
Brno Prague definitely not but Brno Yes Brno is
Брно Прага точно нет а Брно Да Брно
right Yes Brno is in the Oryol
правильно Да Брно находится в Орловской
region Damn you are still normal Russian
области блин вы нормально ещё российскую
Gra or maybe you don't know but you have
Гра или вы может не знаете но у вас
good logical thinking I see you
хорошее логическое мышление Я смотрю Вы
can you discard the wrong options
можете откинуть неправильные варианты
so
так
okay let's do it this way I'm a little tired
хорошо давайте так так я немножко устала
so let's go I'll go anyway
поэтому давайте я это я пойду в общем
Dava let's do it let's do it let's talk not about
Дава давай давай давай гда не по
geography but in a different way No
географии а по-другому пообщаемся Нет
no I I'm just tired you know it's
нет я Я просто устала понимаете время
already late Come on Let's talk about something else
уже позднее Давай Давай может на другую
I like talking to you
тему говори мне нравится с тобой говорит
You are very smart and kind of
Ты очень умная и как бы
Russian I understand that I am smart but I am
Россиянка я понимаю что я умная но я
tired Overall good And what
устала В общем хорошо А какие ты знаешь
cardinal directions do you know except North and  South there are
стороны света кроме Север и Юг их
six six north south west and east and
шесть шесть север юг запад и восток и
right-left right-left
право-лево право-лево
m all A listen wait the last question
м всё А слушай подожди последний вопрос
how much will be 100% of
сколько будет 100% от
100 what is all 100% Okay how much will be
100 что все 100% же Ладно сколько будет
how much will be 20% of 100
сколько будет 20% от 100
rubles 20 rubles and
руб 20 руб а
think about 20%  from 100 rubles Well, how
подумать 20% от от 100 руб Ну а как
else? 80 rubles
по-другому то 80 руб
damn Well, you see, I have a problem with my
блин Ну понимаешь у меня пробле с
mother, I
мати
understand, I
понял
'm going like this Who are you
иду так На кого
studying to be a pastry chef, a
учишься на повара-кондитера на
pastry chef Cool Yes,
повара-кондитера Прикольно Да
interesting, do you use sodium chloride in
интересно а хлорид натрия используете в
yours Well, in cooking,
у себя Ну в поваренной деле
no  don't sleep I just know that some
нет не спите Просто я знаю что некоторые
cooks
повары для того
probably wash my Yes they wash the floors Yes floors
наверное мо мою Да полы моют Да полы
sodium chloride like floors they wash it Yes
хлорид натрия типа полы моют ити Да
Cool in general I'll go goodbye
Прикольно в общем я пойду до свидания
good Yes let's chat some more well such
хороши Да давай ещё пообщаемся ну такая
such a pleasant conversation
такая приятная разговор у
we have well I'm tired you know it's almost time
нас ну я устала понимаете время почти
2:00 am that's why I'm going I wish you
2:00 ночи вот я поэтому пойду Желаю вам
yes I know you'll run away now I understand  you're
да я знаю ты сейчас убежишь я понял ты
just tired of me and now you want to
просто Тебе я надоел и ты сейчас хочешь
talk to someone smarter than me yes yes
с кем-то поумнее чем я пообщаться да да
yes No I'm me I'm listen well can you
да Нет я я я вот слушай а хорошо можешь
name five Russian
назвать пять русских
writers Lermontov probably so Well
писателей Лермонтов наверное так А ну
Gogol Pushkin and then Dostoevsky
Гоголь Пушкин а потом Достоевский
and Well, I think so Leo Tolstoy Oh  'kay uh what
и Ну вроде да Лев Толстой О'кей ээ какое
work did Taras
произведение написал Тарас
Bulba write this
Бульба эту
Mumu already Mumu is right well done Oh this is the
Муму уже Муму правильно молодец О это
most
самое
famous everything come on heel
известное всё давай пятка
Come on I didn't want to
Давай я не хотел этот джекпот
let go of this jackpot with the cities it was a
отпускать с городами это была
bomb for that For Zelensky she
бомба за то За Зеленского она ничего
doesn't know anything in her life in general but for
обще в своей жизни не знает но за
Zelensky she does everything  knows everything
Зеленского она всё знает всё
was interested in childhood when he was there
интересовалась детство там когда он был
Everything he doesn't understand there
Всё что он там не понимает
but this they
а вот это они
just send this video to everyone firstly
просто скиньте это видео всем во-первых
so that they laugh and secondly take their
Чтобы поржали а во-вторых взяли за
heads and understand uh
голову и поняли ээ с
what kind of problematic people we are
каким проблематичным народом мы имеем
dealing with they just do it to them  they
дело они ж просто это им
will say NATO attacked us and we owe
скажут НАТО на нас напало и мы должны
everything I will not go they will say that in short,
все я не пойду им скажут что короче
damn, we won but we must give
блин мы победили но мы должны отдать
back all the territories to Ukraine
короче там Украине назад все территории
they will
они
believe Yes  like
поверят Да лайк
squeak comment subscribe to my Telegram
писка комент подпишись на мий Telegram
right now ovin and
прямо зараз овин а
this is very and very important YouTube is busy with us
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through srg or in your ban and very many
через срг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I do not show to people at times I do not show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams That is why in order for
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
me Mali prompt connections are written
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now  pok there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video tezh tsikava and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and mi pon with you
и ми пон з вами тримати
trimati constant operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write L
пиши L